Jhaal
hey buffalo and maintenance today in this video
we will talk about market forces
how you were able to survive and in this video we will see
how we can do our own so let's
now
school
and after this we took
time in 2016 2017 but the global market
here we have a recovery
[music]
above 1978 and again above 90 from here
we have
some players for this
now let's talk about Nifty so
after drinking here Nifty made a
unit
a bullet low of 1716 and later
after this replacement we
showed a recovery in it in August if we look at some longer time
period then this ascendant
is our 10 top support so if on Monday
you get to see this loan again you will
take a shot on the fat side below it stuff
that people should take options minutes
tell them here
a put buy is happening for above seven six and above
so here we have a best
card contract fat above 30 mothers so this
if those  We have seen actress Swaroop Shivling short
covering, so
in the next few rounds, see here, it can happen,
but for that, the entry here will have to
support Nifty, so guide Abhigya, you have to
consider,
even after it is proved above 2750, we will
take a plate and go back to it and
after that,
you can click on the contact Indramani of 1768
and this is such an officer Dutt, you
can destroy 1766, due to which you will
definitely see the chances of making huge profits in cricket in intraday, which
may change the trailer in the soil, so here is
an interesting fact information and
duty, if you see after placing, here is
this back cover and later on, on the
basis of what I saw here, right now we are
standing above the important break 2011,
if you see yourself above 30920,
at least on Monday, you have to
take laundry above it here and that is
on the source side and above that,
please here we break  Since we will gas by a quarter of an inch,
if it is coming down to 3000 and that is
due to tension, then you can take a
short position below it
on the Parmesan cheese side and you can add your position and
delete this 3878 2011. Guys, after this, let me
tell you for the option traders that here
also we have a fixed time for Begusarai and records,
but
if we will see a surprise in 3908 short covering here, then
after an hour from above 369, we will
start locking in Baikunth here, we can do
whatever is there for that and
Option Pilot here 4000
call in
[Music]
After reducing everything, now let's talk about it
[Music]. The
first name comes,
subscribe
because we show solitaire
here
and now we will see a breakup
with love volume, so
you can share at least nine
British media,
one minute deep
study on this side.  And further you have to
unite this country by feeling your stop loss, those who
should take training in other staff here, so stock monitor former prime,
much before the results came, for at least
10 days we did a use recovery in this topic
here, so talk
recent, then our major register of dowry is
trading on it, so from now on
you need to make a little more rally here,
market
flashlight, if the
market gives here to its people,
then you can also add 1-side in this trick
and our target for it will be this
side of 98100, for this you will debit, then
108 back and stop loss of 205, you
can candy crush in extra classes,
welcome, did you like the video or you
must subscribe to this channel
because here you are given trading lessons without any
speculation with proper guidance,
proper logic, through
which you can grow a healthy baby profit
intraday,
which comes third, this channel
Hindustan  Aeronautics Limited and the stock
is its responsible resistance level here,
after consolidating for the last few days,
we saw a little bit of heart in 3105 Play Store, but now
in the stop on Friday, which has been seen on the side,
due to this, this
previous consolidation which you
can see Bashruddin and here you
can like and comment 3810 because
if it is requested twice again, then you
can easily activate your stop,
in that case, the stop loss will be of 125,
so guide our entry point will be
10 here and we will
serve our Pratik Patil profit at 3000 53522, let
me
tell you that there are chances of Bandhan becoming a little older here
because why
is Bandhan in the tourist bus, now we have clicked on a cement plant of Cheese Cross, so
in the portfolio of guys districts, these topics can
definitely land together because
you have a holiday in the next one week, so  You will definitely see a target of ₹50, so if
we want to take advantage of it intraday, then apply it
forcefully. Take this strip, you can get a
tattoo of up to ₹15 or time
from the internet, your children, your
stoploss is 125 in it and yes,
in intraday you can definitely do your tempered glass,
so finally if you match some
recent videos in this and upcoming videos, then the
heroine who is in the IPO is the second
technique, totally call me Hussain,
subscribe and see on current activation,
you found a very good subject plastic
Bachchan in it, so if you have
not invested in it yet, then you
can apply for a single minute because
overall the valuation of this IPO is quite high,
edit 10, take it out on paper
and if you do it in the grey market, then you can easily
get above 60 in the market, after this, now let's talk about the
policy market, here this
and
about it we will give you a tweet on our page, so
if you had not done 299, then
definitely mix something again,  Through it
because it is there before the market opens,
so such important things and
strawmen are done, suicide, there are
good chances of slipping in it too, so you
wait for at least one group meeting
and on the last day you
can proceed in it according to your option, so
for today not in this video, if you have
created a channel then definitely like and subscribe
because such updates are
not listed right now,
in the next video
definitely watch us for a few more minutes, whichever way
I may get
you, thank you so
much exam start electronically
[Music]